<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mobile_app_CA1_23643_LucianoGimenez</string>
    <string name="full_name">Luciano Gimenez</string>
    <string name="email">23643@student.dorset-college.ie</string>
    <string name="intro">More than 8 years of managerial and administrative experience provided me with the ability to work in teams and moulded me into an entrepreneur. Throughout my education I gained knowledge for managing services industry, project planning and business development. Looking for a position to further polish my skills and build on my experience.</string>
    <string name="education">Education</string>
    <string name="skills">Skills</string>
    <string name="hobbies">Hobbies</string>
    <string name="achievements">Achievements</string>
    <string name="copyright">© Copyright Luciano Gimenez 2022</string>
    <string name="copyright_2">Built with Android Studio</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="educationRow1Institute">Dorset College, Ireland</string>
    <string name="educationRow1Title">BACHELOR’S DEGREE: COMPUTING</string>
    <string name="educationRow1Description">Completed the first year by passing the exams in Computer Fundamentals, Computational Thinking and Problem-Solving, Interpersonal Skills for IT, UX/UI Design and Usability, Programming Essentials, Management Information Systems, Networking Technologies, Mathematics, and Software-Defined Computing. Gaining all the necessary skills to work in software development, computer programming, cyber-security, and computer networks settings.</string>
    <string name="educationRow2Institute">National University of Rosario, Argentina</string>
    <string name="educationRow2Title">BACHELOR’S DEGREE: PRODUCTION OF GOODS AND SERVICES</string>
    <string name="educationRow2Description">Completed a technical program focused on physics, mathematics, computer science, goods production and management, as well as operational logistics.</string>
    <string name="educationRow3Institute">Rice University, Coursera online</string>
    <string name="educationRow3Title">CERTIFICATE: FUNDAMENTALS OF COMPUTING SPECIALIZATION</string>
    <string name="educationRow3Description">The specialization covers interactive programming in Python, principles of computing, and algorithmic thinking. Upon completion, will be able to carry out object-oriented programming (OOP), understand algorithms, and be familiar with graph theory and tree data structure.</string>
    <string name="educationRow4Institute">CISCO Networking Academy, online</string>
    <string name="educationRow4Title">CERTIFICATE: SWITCHING, ROUTING, AND WIRELESS ESSENTIALS</string>
    <string name="educationRow4Description">Acquiring skills needed to configure and troubleshoot VLANs, Wireless LANs, and Inter-VLAN routing and troubleshoot redundancy on a switched network using STP and EtherChannel.</string>
    <string name="educationRow5Title">CERTIFICATE: NDG LINUX ESSENTIALS</string>
    <string name="educationRow5Description">Gaining an understanding of how Linux is used and mastering Linux commands.</string>
    <string name="educationRow6Title">CERTIFICATE: INTRODUCTION TO NETWORKS</string>
    <string name="educationRow6Description">Able to build simple LANs, perform basic configurations for routers and switches, and implement IPv4 and IPv6 addressing schemes while adhering to security best practices.</string>
    <string name="skillRow1">Java</string>
    <string name="skillRow2">Python</string>
    <string name="skillrow3">C#</string>
    <string name="skillrow4">MySQL</string>
    <string name="skillrow5">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="skillrow6">Microsoft Azure</string>
    <string name="skillrow7">HTML</string>
    <string name="skillrow8">JavaScript</string>
    <string name="skillrow9">Node.js</string>
</resources>